Guide to the Voices Breaking Boundaries Records
University of Houston Libraries
- Digital Media
  - Media on Discs
    - DVDs
      - Iraq in Fragments - James Longley (Dvd 69-74)
      - Harvest of Hope (Dvd 75)
      - Readings from Voices of a People's History of the United States By Howard Zinn and Anthony Arnove (Dvd 76)
      - VBB DVD2 (Dvd 77)
      - VBB @ Wesley Community Center, 9/28/2007 (Dvd 78)
      - Patti Smith Live! at Cullen Performance Hall, 4.19.10, presented by Voices Breaking Boundaries (Dvd 79)
      - Autobiography in 5 chapters, April 2013 (Dvd 80-81)
      - VBB - Homes and History Art Event - Freedman Town, Houston - 12-1-12, Burnell McCray Photographer, burnell.mccray@att.net, (H)281.481.1558, (C)225.620.6592 (Dvd 82)
      - VBB 10-Year Anniversary, QT File (Dvd 83)
      - VBB WFP4 (Dvd 84)
      - 8-4-08, Brown in the Third Ward, Conversation b/w Priutt, Sheba and Ivette (filmed by Eric Hester) (Dvd 85)
      - Recording Session, Friday December 9, 2005, Lee High School Performers (Dvd 86-88)
      - VBB, Dinner, Cafe Flores Video, Eric Hester (Dvd 89)
      - VBBDVD (Dvd 90)
      - VBB Incite Summer! Voices Breaking Boundaries, 23 June 05 (Dvd 91)
      - VBB Calendar (Dvd 92)
      - Recording Session, Lee High School (Dvd 93-94)
      - Voices Breaking Boundaries, Spring Spam 2007 (Dvd 95)
      - Haya Fatima Igbal (Dvd 96)
      - Alice INterview, 30 min, edited by Yunuen Perez Vertti (Dvd 97)
      - DVD for Nov 5, Art Car Compilation (Dvd 98)
      - Patti Smith, DVD Loop, Concert Only (Dvd 99)
      - Kitcheners, Autumn_Sehba (Dvd 100)
      - Daniel Bustamante (Dvd 101)
      - East Meets West, Attachment D, Grant # 10550058, November 2009 (Dvd 102)
      - Sheba, From Our Interior (Dvd 103)
      - Jump Abijon (Dvd 104)
      - Khrusrau-i-Nasl-i-Nav, Loop for LRA w/title (Dvd 105)
      - 2012 NEA (Dvd 106)
      - Back Screen "Revolution", Master DVD, Art Car Parade, 2011 (Dvd 107)
      - Backscreen "Revolution", Master DVD, Art Car Parade, 2011 (Dvd 108)
      - VBB Documentary 2011 - Rough Cut (for Valiente 2011) (Dvd 109)
      - Bindiya Chamkay Gi, Ragni Kidvai, 28 mins (Dvd 110)
      - VBB, Eric Hester, VBB 2009-10 Photos (Dvd 111)
      - Pakistan Floods, YouTube Videos (Dvd 112)
      - Pakistan Floods, Original, 21 min (Dvd 113)
      - Pakistan Floods, Slideshow (Dvd 114)
      - I...am a woman, a film by Sheheezad Kaleen, Runtime: 30 minutes (Dvd 115)
      - VBB Promotional Video (Dvd 116)
      - Carnival Dominicano (Dvd 117)
      - Valiente 2011, Bapsi Sidhwa (Dvd 118)
      - VBB Videos: 1) Valiente 2011 and 2) Decade of Dissent, Data Files, Mov (Dvd 119)
      - Nov 7, 2009, Living Room Art, Honoring Dissent, 7 min (Dvd 120)
      - Why Are You Looking at Me? by Sehba Sanwar (Dvd 121)
      - Vbb Decade Promo-1 (Dvd 122)
    - Other discs
      - 3.5 Floppy disc: VBB (Disk 35FL01)
      - Zip Disc: Jesse H. Jones, December 2001 issue (Disk ZIP01)
      - Zip disc: VBB (Disk ZIP02)
  - Archived webpages for VBB Past Events
    https://web.archive.org/web/20161020163950/http:/vbbarts.org/p-events.shtml
  - University of Houston History 6383 interviews
    Interviews produced as a part of the University of Houston course History 6383 in fall 2014 taught by Professor Kairn Klieman. Most interviews consist of .mp3 audio files as well as .docx transcripts. Some also include video. Interviews missing release forms are marked [closed]. Files saved at 2014-015_001_vbb.
    - Frank_Aguilar_Recording.MP3 (Item 1)
    - Aguilar_Frank_Transcript.docx (Item 2)
    - Abrego-Pena_Carmen_Transcript.docx (Item 3)
    - Castillo_Jimmy_recording.MP3 (Item 4)
    - Castillo_Jimmy_Transcript.doc (Item 5)
    - Marcela_Descalzi_Recording.mp3 (Item 6)
    - Marcella_Descalzi_Recording.mp3 (Item 7)
    - Descalzi_Maria_transcript.docx (Item 8)
    - Ana_Laurel_audio (#1).MP3 [closed] (Item 9)
    - Laurel_Ana_Transcript.docx [closed] (Item 10)
    - Martinez_Karen_Recording.m4a (Item 11)
    - Martinez_Karen_Transcript.docx (Item 12)
    - Mercedes_Negron_Recording.mp3 [closed] (Item 13)
    - Negron-Perez_Mercedes_transcript.docx [closed] (Item 14)
    - Perez_Yunuen_Recording.m4a (Item 15)
    - Perez-Vertti_ Yunuen_Transcript .docx (Item 16)
    - Sarwar_Sehba_video (#1pt.1).MTS (Item 17)
    - Sarwar_Sehba_video (#2).MTS (Item 18)
    - Sarwar_Sehba_video (#3).MTS (Item 19)
    - Sehba_Sarwar_Recording (#2a).MP3 (Item 20)
    - Sehba_Sarwar_Recording (#2b).MP3 (Item 21)
    - Sehba_Sarwar_Recording (#2c).MP3 (Item 22)
    - Sarwar_Sehba_recording (#3).dct (Item 23)
    - Sarwar (1)_Sehba_Transcript.docx (Item 24)
    - Sarwar (2)_Sehba_Transcript.docx (Item 25)
    - Sarwar (3)_Sehba_Transcript.docx (Item 26)
    - Shah_Jacsun_Transcript.docx (Item 27)
    - Shahdin_Kamruzzaman_Written Response.docx (Item 28)
    - Turner_Joshua_recording.m4a (Item 29)
    - Turner_Joshua_Transcript.doc (Item 30)
    - Woodson_Michael_Transcript.docx (Item 31)